(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
sweets parade
作詞：uRy 作曲：CHI-MEY
Lyrics: uRy Composition: CHI-MEY
あいうえお菓子した かきくけこんなにも
A-I-U-E-O Sweetened snacks, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Such a lot.
さしすせソフトクリーム ごーらーらっぺでいごー
Sa-Shi-Su-Se Soft-serve ice cream, Go-Ra-Ra-Pe-Dei-Go.
たちつてトトってきいたのに なねのデリシャス
Ta-Chi-Tsu-Te-To, I heard it, Na-Ne-No Delicious.
はひふへホットパイ みんなでのこのこ
Ha-Hi-Fu-He Hot pie, everyone coming along.
ショートケーキふわり
Shortcake, fluffy.
キャンディペロペロ
Candy, lick-lick.
チョコレートの川で
In the river of chocolate.
わたがしガムみたい
Cotton candy is like gum.
アイスクリームの塔
Tower of ice cream.
プリンのお城で
At the pudding castle.
カスタードわたぬき
Custard Watanuki.
二人のランデブー
A rendezvous for the two of us.
カフェ色サンデー
Coffee-colored sundae.
あんこもハッピー
Anko is happy too.
たいやきにクリーム
Taiyaki with cream.
小悪魔ドロップ
Little devil drops.
カップケーキから
From cupcakes.
イチゴあんみつまで
To strawberry anmitsu.
好境なスイーツ
Excellent sweets.
仲良くなれるよ
We can become good friends.
ホ～ンより 夢見てごらん
Take a look at a slight dream.
キャラメル みたいにくっつこう
Let's stick together like caramel.
ハミムメモもっと ラリリルレロルケーキ
Ha-Mi-Mu-Me-Mo more, Ra-Ri-Ru-Re-Ro Roll cake.
わおんわおんお菓子は タヌキときどき嘘
Wa-On Wa-On, sweets are tanuki and sometimes lies.
あいうえお菓子した かきくけこんなにも
A-I-U-E-O Sweetened snacks, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Such a lot.
さしすせソフトクリーム ごーらーらっぺでいごー
Sa-Shi-Su-Se Soft-serve ice cream, Go-Ra-Ra-Pe-Dei-Go.
のみにハヤベン
Fast lunch at the flea market.
焼きのり炙って
Toasting roasted seaweed.
おにぎりコロコロ
Onigiri rolling along.
友達ホカホカ
Friends are warm and toasty.
もみじ饅頭と
Momiji manju and...
あんぱんお月様
Anpan Moon.
わたぬきに始まり
Beginning with Watanuki.
わたぬきに終わる日々
Days ending with Watanuki.
ホ～ンのり 見つめてごらん
Take a slight look.
甘くて 苦い夕焼け
A sweet and bitter sunset.
たちつてトトってきいたのに なねのデリシャス
Ta-Chi-Tsu-Te-To, I heard it, Na-Ne-No Delicious.
はひふへホットパイ みんなでのこのこ
Ha-Hi-Fu-He Hot pie, everyone coming along.
ハミムメモもっと ラリリルレロルケーキ
Ha-Mi-Mu-Me-Mo more, Ra-Ri-Ru-Re-Ro Roll cake.
わおんわおんお菓子は タヌキときどき嘘
Wa-On Wa-On, sweets are tanuki and sometimes lies.
ミルフィーユワッフル ボンボン蒸しわたぬきパイ
Mille-feuille waffles, Bon-bon steamed Watanuki pie.
シュークリームバナナゼリー ボンボロワタヌキ
Cream puffs, banana jelly, Bon-boro-Watanuki.
ホットケーキバウムクーヘン わたぬきわたぬき
Pancakes, Baumkuchen, Watanuki Watanuki.
わたわたわたぬきクレープ わたぬきわたぬき
Wata-wata-Watanuki crepes, Watanuki Watanuki.
わたぬきとご飯
Watanuki and rice.
わたぬきとおやつ
Watanuki and snacks.
わたぬきと肉まん
Watanuki and meat buns.
わたぬき
Watanuki.
Sweets Parade
わたのき べっこうあめ
Cotton tree, amber sugar
いちごあめ わたのき
Strawberry candy, cotton tree
わたのき シロップ
Cotton tree, syrup
あんずあめ わたのき
Apricot candy, cotton tree
おむね わたのき ラム
Chest, cotton tree, rum
こんがり 思い出色
Deeply toasted, the color of memories
はちみつみたいだけど
It's like honey, but...
あいうえお菓子した
A-I-U-E-O, we made some sweets
かきくけこんなにも
Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke, so much of it
さしすせそっとクリーム
Sa-Shi-Su-Se, gently with cream
ごぞうろっぷで行こう
Let's go with all our heart
たちつて飛んできた
Ta-Chi-Tsu-Te, it flew over here
なにぬねのりしお
Na-Ni-Nu-Ne, seaweed salt
はひふへほんとバイト
Ha-Hi-Fu-He, really, just a bite
ふたりでロックンロール
The two of us, rock 'n' roll
まみむめモンブラン
Ma-Mi-Mu-Me, Mont Blanc
やいゆえヨーグルト
Ya-I-Yu-E, yogurt
らりるれロールケーキ
Ra-Ri-Ru-Re, roll cake
わたのきとキッス
A kiss with the cotton tree
わたのきの甘み わたのきの苦み
The sweetness and bitterness of the cotton tree
わたのきの酸味で 好き好きラブコンボ！
With its sourness, I love you, love combo!
んなー！みんな、おるよー！
Nna! Everyone, are you there?!
ホロライブ4期生 姫森ルーナななななー！
Hololive 4th Gen, Himemori Luna-na-na-na!
みんな見に来てくれてありがちゅう！
Thank you all for coming to see me!
今日は素敵なゲストと 重大告知があるのらので
Today, I have a wonderful guest and a big announcement,
最後までお楽しみにー！
So please look forward to it until the very end!
エレクトーン発表会
Electone Recital
人生のメリーゴーランド
Merry-Go-Round of Life
うーわ！ルーナの演奏どうだった？
Whoa! How was Luna's performance?
ちょっとね、ミスしちゃったけど、頑張って弾いたのらよ。
I made a few mistakes, but I did my best to play it.
みんな、どうだった？
Everyone, how was it?
みんなのちょっとコメント見るのら。
I'll check everyone's comments for a bit.
最高だった、素晴らしい。ありがとう。
“It was the best,” “wonderful.” Thank you!
おー、なんかもう胸がいっぱい。ふふふ。
Oh, my heart is so full! Hehe.
みんな、見てくれてありがとう。
Everyone, thanks for watching!
まずね、弾けたことと、あと最初、あのね、ルーナのこの、
First of all, I was able to play it, and I also wanted to...
エレクトーンをね、みんなにね、見せたいなーって思うのら。
...show everyone Luna's Electone!
これ凄くない？ルーナ仕様のね、エレクトーンなのらよ。
Isn't this amazing? It's a Luna-customized Electone!
これ、今日のためにね、運営さんがね、用意してくれました。
The staff prepared this for today!
見て、もうちょっとみんなに、細部を見てもらいたいのら。
Look, I want everyone to see the details a bit more!
見て、ここに『hololive』って書いてあるでしょ？
Look, it says “hololive” here, right?
ここもね、お月様と星様がついて、ふわふわーってなって、めちゃくちゃ可愛いのら！
Here too, with the moon and stars, and it's all fluffy... it's super cute!
やばくない？ここちょっと一周して...
Isn't it crazy? Let's go around here...
こっちもね、凄いでしょ？
This side too, amazing right?
これ凄いのらー！ルーナが使ってるね、マイクもあるし。
This is amazing! There's even the mic that Luna uses!
もうね、最高！今日のためにね、ルーナの、今までね、練習してきたね...
It's just the best! For today, all of Luna's practice so far...
エレクトーンのね、発表会のために、準備してくれました。
They prepared it for the Electone recital!
ちょっとここね、足のところ、透けるのら。ちょっと見て欲しいのら。
The area around the pedals is transparent. I want you to see it!
見える？ルーナ見える、みんな？ルーナのこと見えてる？
Can you see? Can you see Luna, everyone? Can you see me?
おるよ、ここに。ふふふ。
I'm right here! Hehe.
エレクトーンもすごいね、
The Electone is amazing too,
可愛すぎてもう、今すごい緊張しドキドキなのらよ。
it's so cute that I'm really nervous and my heart is pounding right now.
まあこれね、ルーナがね、今年のね、
Well, you see, Luna...
6月からね、本格的にエレクトーンの配信ができるようになって。
since June of this year, I've been able to stream Electone properly.
1年前はね、誕生日にピアノのお披露目をしたんだけど。
A year ago, I debuted my piano on my birthday.
今年からエレクトーンができるようになって、
Since I started doing Electone this year,
みんなにね、エレクトーン癒されるとか、エレクトーン配信大好きって言ってもらえるようになって。
everyone tells me it's healing or that they love the Electone streams.
今日、この日ルーナの誕生祭でね、お披露目ができて、
And today, being able to perform it at Luna's Birthday Festival,
本当に本当に嬉しいのら。
makes me really, really happy.
もう今本当ドキドキがヤバい。
My heart is pounding so much right now.
ふふ。ちょっとミスっちゃったけど、それはもうお愛嬌なのらよね。
Hehe. I made a little mistake, but that's just a bit of charm, right?
いつもの通りお愛嬌でちょっとね。バレへん、バレへんなのら。
Just like usual, a bit of charm... No one noticed, no one noticed!
みんなのおかげで、今こうしてね、素敵なね、エレクトーンで演奏することができました。
Thanks to everyone, I was able to perform on this wonderful Electone.
いつもね、聴いてくれてありがちゅ。
Thank you always for listening.
これからもね、聴いてくれたら嬉しい。
I'd be happy if you continue to listen.
ありがとね。
Thanks!
ではここからは、スペシャルなゲストが待っているのらね。
Now, from here, a special guest is waiting!
次のコーナーに行くのらーい！
Let's go to the next corner!
ということで、ここからはゲストの2人が来てくれるのら！どうぞー！
So, from here, two guests are coming! Please come in!
わー！来たのらー！
Waaaaa! We're here!
ありがとう！今日はね、このお二人に来ていただきました。お挨拶どうぞ。
Thank you! Today, these two have come. Please introduce yourselves.
しゃー！ホロライブ2期生、大空スバルです！ルーナおめでとう！
Yes! Hololive 2nd Gen, Oozora Subaru here! Luna, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はーい！ホロライブ2期生悪魔の保健医、癒月ちょこです。ルーナ様おめでとうございます！
Hi! Hololive 2nd Gen demon nurse, Yuzuki Choco. Luna-sama, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm happy!
いやということでね、今回はルーナ様の誕生日ということで、スバルとわたくしがルーナ様のお願い叶えちゃおうかなって思うんだけど。
So, since it's Luna-sama's birthday, Subaru and I want to grant Luna-sama's wish.
え、本当？本当？え、何でもいいのら？
Really? Really? Anything?
何でもいいとは言ってないのら。
I didn't say "anything."
何、何したいの、ルーナ様。
What do you want to do, Luna-sama?
えー、じゃあ、いっぱいあるんだけど、えーじゃあ...
Well, I have many... but then...
1個だけ？1個だけ。
Just one? Just one.
1個、1個。
One, one.
じゃあまずケーキ食べたいのら。
First, I want to eat cake!
お、いいね！
Oh, that's good!
スバルとちょこ先生に食べさせてもらいたい。
I want Subaru and Choco-sensei to feed me.
しょうがないわねー。しょうがないなー。
Can't be helped. Can't be helped.
ケーキ、出でよ！わっ！
Cake, appear! Whoa!
うお！ケーキだ！
Whoa! A cake!
え、こんなにデカいの出てくる？
Wait, such a big one appeared?
めちゃめちゃデカい！
It's huge!
ルーナ、魔法使えるから。
Because Luna can use magic.
おい、適当言うなよお前。
Hey, don't just say whatever.
初めて聞いたぞそんなの。
I've never heard of that before.
食べさせて、食べさせて！
Feed me, feed me!
しょうがない、じゃあハッピーバースデー歌いながら食べさせるか。
Can't be helped, let's feed you while singing Happy Birthday.
歌ってくれるのら？
You'll sing for me?
いくよ、スバル。
Ready, Subaru?
ちょっと待って、その前に。
Wait, before that.
出でよ、フォーク！はっ！
Appear, fork! Ha!
え？
Eh?
おい、フライングしてんじゃねえか、ちょこ先生。
Hey, you're stealing a piece already, Choco-sensei.
え、何かしら？
Eh? What could it be?
何かしらじゃねえよ。
It's not "what could it be!"
いつの間に取ったんだお前。
When did you take that?
早業すぎねえかお前。
Aren't you too fast?
まあまあ、先にね、食べちゃった。
Well, I ate first.
待って、なんで誕生日の方より先に食べてんの？
Wait, why are you eating before the birthday girl?
違う違う違う、これは...
No, no, no, this is...
せーの。
Ready, go.
ハッピーバースデー・トゥー・ルーナ
Happy Birthday to Luna
え、ここでも食べてる？
Eh, are you eating here too?
ハッピーバースデー
Happy Birthday
顔被ってる！
Your faces are overlapping!
え、もう食べてる？
Eh, already eating?
ディアー・ルーナ
dear Luna
ハッピーバースデー・トゥー・ルーナ
Happy Birthday to Luna
うれしい！ふー。
Happy! (Blows out candle)
1歳おめでとう！おめでとう！
Happy 1st Birthday! Congratulations!
いや、1歳じゃねえから。
No, it's not the 1st birthday.
え、1歳じゃないの？
Eh, not the 1st birthday?
いや、だってルーナ去年も誕生日迎えたけど、0歳だったぞ。
Well, Luna had a birthday last year too, and she was 0 years old then.
ガチ？じゃあ0歳なの？
Seriously? So she's 0 years old?
そうだったぞ。
That's how it was.
何ドヤ顔してんだよ。そういうことじゃねえよ。
Why that smug face? That's not how it works.
0歳なのら！へへ。
I'm 0 years old! Hehe.
待て待て待て！
Wait, wait, wait!
じゃあケーキも食べたし。
Well, we've eaten the cake.
え、待って、早くない？
Eh, wait, isn't that too fast?
え、そろそろ？
Is it time already?
え、待って待って待って。
Wait, wait, wait.
早いって、早いって！
Too fast, too fast!
お誕生日祝ったしね！
We celebrated your birthday!
じゃあ、そういうことで。 待って、待って！
Well then, that's it. Wait, wait!
あとも頑張って。 いや待てよ！
Good luck with the rest. No, wait!
おい、語尾抜けてるぞ。「待てよ」じゃねぇよ。
Hey, you forgot your catchphrase! It's not "Wait."
「のら」抜けてるぞお前！ 大丈夫か？
You forgot the "nanora"! Are you okay?
素に戻ってるぞ！ アイデンティティが！
You're going back to normal! Your identity!
おい、待てよ... あっ、待て、のら。
Hey, wait... Oh, wait, nanora.
ルーナも二人にも食べさせてえのらけど。
Luna wants you two to eat some too, nanora.
お、本当？！ 食べさせてくれるの？
Oh, really?! You'll let us eat some?
お、お嬢様～！ いいの？！
Oh, princess! Is it okay?!
ほら！ え、怖っ！
Here! Whoa, scary!
ケーキを前にすると性格変わるの？ ほら、ほら！
Does your personality change in front of cake? Here, here!
ほらほらほら！ 食わせる気なさすぎだろ！
Come on, come on! You're being too aggressive!
あーん、あーん、あーん、あーん！ イエーイ！
Ahn, ahn, ahn, ahn! Yay!
美味しかった。 ほら！
It was delicious. Here!
ほらっ！ え、へへ。 はい！
There! Hehe. Here!
ほらスバ、はい食べて。 はい、はい。
Here Suba, eat up. Yes, yes.
アムアムアム。 あ、食べさせ合いっこ！ アムアムアム！
Amm amm amm. Oh, feeding each other! Amm amm amm!
うめぇ！ うめぇ！ うめぇのら！
Delicious! Delicious! It's delicious, nanora!
止まれない！ チョコ先生！ あらあら！
I can't stop! Choco-sensei! Oh my!
スバ、ありがとう！
Suba, thank you!
ほらルーナたん、もっとお食べ。 あたべ、あむあむあむ。
Here Luna-tan, eat more. Oh, amm amm amm.
足りないのら！ ほらアムアムアム。 顔に生クリームが！
It's not enough! Amm amm amm. Cream on your face!
何自分で食ってんの？！ しょうがないのら！
Why are you eating yourself?! I can't help it, nanora!
満足しましたか、ルーナさん？
Are you satisfied now, Luna-san?
うん、満足したけど。 まだね、まだね。
Yeah, I'm satisfied, but... there's more, there's more.
なんだよ。 まだお願いしたいことがあるのら。
What is it? I still have something I want to ask, nanora.
何よ、言ってみなさいよ。 聞いてくれる？
What is it? Just tell us. Will you listen?
まあ内容によるけど。 あのね...
Well, it depends on what it is. Um, you see...
ルーナ、スバにね、告白して欲しいのら！
Luna wants Suba to confess to her, nanora!
帰りま～す！ お疲れ様でしたー！
I'm going home! Thank you for today!
おい待てよ！ 語尾抜けてる、語尾抜けてる！
Hey, wait! You forgot your catchphrase!
スバにね、告白してもらって。
I want Suba to confess to me.
その瞬間をチョコ先生にカメラで収めて欲しいのら！
And I want Choco-sensei to film that moment, nanora!
いや撮らせてほしい！ いいのかそんな人工的に作られた愛情で！
I'd love to film it! Is it really okay with love created so artificially?!
いいんです！ いいんです、いいんです！
It's fine! It's fine, it's fine!
こいつ今日は気合いが違うぞ。 しょうがねぇな...
She's on another level today. Oh well...
え、やった！ じゃあせっかくだから、いい感じの雰囲気のところでやりたいのら。
Yay! Since we're doing it, I want to do it somewhere with a good atmosphere, nanora.
外に出るのら！ オーケー！ よっしゃ、みんな行くぞ！
Let's go outside, nanora! Okay! Alright, everyone let's go!
せーの、おいしょー！
One, two, hup!
わあー！ 着いた！ きれいなのら！
Whoa! We're here! It's beautiful, nanora!
素敵なところに来ちゃった。 ロマンチック！
We've come to a wonderful place. So romantic!
ロマンチックなのら、ここ。 すごいね。
It's romantic here. It's amazing.
で、ここでやんの？ え、それはもちろんのら！
So, are we doing it here? Well, of course, nanora!
スバに愛の告白を、ルーナにしてもらいたいとのらよ。
Luna wants Suba to give her a confession of love, nanora!
よし、帰ろう。 帰るな！
Alright, let's go home. Don't go!
来たばっかだろ！ 怖い怖い、今日めっちゃ語尾強いな。
We just got here! It's scary, she's really pushy today.
分かった、分かった。 まあ誕生日だもんね、一回ぐらいいいよ。
Alright, alright. It's your birthday after all, so just once is fine.
最後じゃないよ！ これからも、あるけど！
It's not the last time! There will be more to come!
あ、まあそれは置いといて。 じゃあやりましょう！
Uh, well leave that aside. Let's do it!
え、ちょっと待って！ 何だよ？
Wait, just a minute! What is it?
いやね、ここでね、ただ普通にやってもつまらないってことで。
Well, you see, it would be boring to just do it normally here.
つまんなくはないだろ！ チョコから三つ、お題を出します！
It wouldn't be boring! I'll give you three conditions!
何何何何？ まずはね、第一段階。
What, what, what? First, stage one.
二人の距離が縮まっていくって感じでね。 手と手が触れ合うところ！
The distance between you two narrows... and your hands touch!
ああ、いい！ なるほど。 そして第二！
Ah, nice! I see. And second!
もちろんね、二人のハグも見たいから！
Of course, I want to see you two hug too!
アッチッチー！ 最高！ そして最後に、三つ目！
So hot! The best! And finally, the third one!
何何何何？ 三つもあるのかよ。 二人のどっちかが...
What, what? There's a third? One of you...
ほっぺにチュってしちゃう！ ええー！！
Gives a kiss on the cheek! Whaaa?!
お互いがもう抑えきれなくなって、スバの方からも我慢できなくなって！
Neither of you can hold back anymore, and Suba won't be able to resist!
ルーナに！ それは... まあまあまあ。
And goes for Luna! That's... well, well.
やばい、言葉失っちゃった今。 あれ？
Oh man, I'm speechless. Huh?
これはルーナたんのお誕生日ということで。 チョコ的に取り入れたら...
This is for Luna-tan's birthday. I thought if I added this...
ルーナたんが喜ぶかなっていう、シチュエーションの助言をちょっとしようかなって。
It might make Luna-tan happy. Just a little situational advice.
さすがシチュエーションの女王は言うことが違うのらね。 いやいやそんな！
As expected of the Situation Queen, your words are on another level. No, not at all!
ルーナ様は怖いのら、こいつ。 じゃあ、やりますか。
Luna-sama is scary. Well then, shall we do it?
お、ちょっといいところにベンチあるのらよ。 なるほどね。
Oh, there's a nice bench right there. I see.
ここで出会って... ごめん、やばい、記憶なくなっちゃった。 何するんだっけ？
Meet here... sorry, oh no, I've lost my memory. What was I supposed to do?
出会って、座って、手と手触れ合って、ドキドキしながら座るから愛の告白をして。
Meet, sit down, hands touch, and then you confess your love while feeling nervous.
ハグをして、最後にどっちかからチュって。 ほっぺにチュしたらいいんじゃないかなって。
Give a hug, and finally one of us gives a kiss. A kiss on the cheek would be good.
チョコは思うの。 分かりました！
That's what I think. Got it!
素敵！ じゃあしましょう。 じゃあちょっとチョコ、カメラ撮ってくるね。
Wonderful! Let's do it. I'll go get the camera ready.
やった！ チョコ先が撮るの？！ さすがカメラマン！
Yay! Choco-sen is filming?! As expected of the camera operator!
さすがシチュエーションの女王。 いやもう任せてくださいよカメラアングルは！
As expected of the Situation Queen. Leave the camera angles to me!
なるほどね。 じゃあ座ろ座ろ。 座るか。 失礼します。
I see. Let's sit, let's sit. Shall we sit? Excuse me.
はい、失礼します。 あっ、スバ、隣！
Yes, excuse me. Oh, Suba, you're next to me!
隣にいるよ、スバ。 隣にいるのら。
I'm right next to you, Suba. I'm right next to you, nanora.
え、これ、まだ、ここは、知り合いじゃないってこと？
Wait, so we're still strangers at this point?
そう。
Right.
だから、もうちょっと、離れて座っていいかも。
So you should probably sit a bit further away.
え、どこ、どこからモゾモゾするの？
Wait, where? Where should I start fidgeting from?
いや、モゾ... モゾモゾしないの！
No, don't... Don't fidget!
モゾモゾ、モゾモゾ...
*Fidgeting around*
怖い！ ねえ、お、お...
You're scary! Hey, you...
おばあちゃんじゃないよ。
I'm not a grandma.
あ、なるほどね、分かりました。
Ah, I see. Got it.
はい。それじゃあ、お二人とも準備はよろしくて？
Alright. Are you both ready?
うん。
Yup.
それでは、また...
Well then, let's...
ちょっと待って。
Wait a sec.
よし。
Okay.
可愛い。
Cute.
気合入れてくれてるのね。
You're getting all fired up.
いや、入れてません、ちょっとね、今全ての気持ちを吐き出して...
No, I'm not. I'm just letting all my feelings out right now...
よし、やるぞ！
Alright, let's do this!
やるぞ、やるぞ！ メンタル、フィジカル！
Let's go! Mental, physical!
よし。
Alright.
それでは、そんなスバルさんとルーナさんの...
Well then, here's Subaru and Luna's...
イチャイチャ告白まで。3、2、1、アクト！
Flirty confession skit. 3, 2, 1, Action!
あ、今日も疲れたなー。
Man, another tiring day.
え、スバ、何で疲れてるの？
Oh, Suba? Why are you tired?
すいません、知り合いじゃないんですけど、あの...
I'm sorry, I don't know you, but...
あの、あ、どなたですか？
Um, who are you?
どなたですか？ 初めまして。
Who are you? Nice to meet you.
初めまして。あの...
Nice to meet you. Um...
あ、二人の出会い。
Ah, their first meeting.
わ、わたくし、ルーナと申しますが...
My, my name is Luna, but...
ずっとあなたのことを見ていました。
I've been watching you for a long time.
あ、そうなんですか。えっと、いつ、どこで...
Oh, really? Um, when and where...
いきなり告白か？
Confessing right away?!
え、もう、もう生まれた瞬間からずっと見ていたのなのよ。
Well, I've been watching you since the very moment you were born.
僕も。
Me too.
スバルもここで手を打つの。言葉で詰まっている。
Subaru's playing along now. She's at a loss for words.
スバルも、あの、なんか、生まれた時から何か...
I've also, um, since the moment I was born...
え、怖い、怖い... 何、何？
Wait, that's creepy... What? What?
生まれた瞬間の脳裏に過ったのが、この顔だなって丁度思ってたところなんです。
I was just thinking that yours was the face that crossed my mind when I was born.
本当に？
Really?
なんだその双子みたいな言い訳。
What kind of twin-like excuse is that?
嬉しい。
I'm so happy.
これは運命っていうやつなのら。
This must be what they call fate.
もしかしたら運命かもしれないです。
It might just be fate.
嬉しい。
I'm so happy.
何、何ですか？ どうしたんですか、皆さん？
What? What is it? What's wrong, everyone?
ちょっと、嬉しすぎ、嬉しすぎて...
I'm just too, too happy...
手を触りたいのか、手を二度見したわ、今。
She looks like she wants to touch her hand. She just did a double take at it.
あの... スバルさんに触れてもいいですか？
Um... May I touch you, Subaru-san?
はい。
Yes.
おっと、ここでルーナたんが手をベンチに置くのか...
Oh, Luna's putting her hand on the bench...
スバルどうしたらいいですか？ 積極的なのか、どっちなのか、これは...
What should I do? Is she being aggressive or what? Which is it...?
あ、あ、手、触れたいな。
Ah, I want to touch your hand.
じゃ、手を繋ぎましょう。
Then let's hold hands.
繋げるかな...
I wonder if we can...
上手く繋げるかな...
I wonder if they can do it properly...
何で逃げるんですか？
Why are you running away?
あ、触れている... 触れている...
Ah, we're touching... We're touching...
体温を感じるよ。
I can feel your warmth.
あ、本当ですか？
Ah, really?
スバ、スバの温かみを感じる。
I can feel Suba's warmth.
や、実はスバルも、なんかこの体温から、なんだかルーナさんはとても素敵な人なんじゃないかなと思い始めました。
Actually, I've also started thinking that from this warmth, Luna-san must be a very wonderful person.
本当に？
Really?
これ、もう少し体温感じたいのでハグしませんか？
I'd like to feel more of your warmth, so would you like to hug?
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
スバルのセリフが棒読みなんだけど。
Subaru's delivery is so robotic.
もっと心込めて。
Put more heart into it.
ちょっと、実はスバルも、なんか、もうちょっと触れ合いたいなと思ったので...
Actually, I've also been thinking that I want to be a bit closer to you, so...
あの、ハグしてもいいですか？
Um, may I hug you?
もちろん！
Of course!
じゃあ、ハグしましょう。
Then, let's hug.
立ちましょう。
Let's stand up.
あ、立って、立ってしたいんですね。
Oh, so you want to do it standing up.
あ、そんな直立不動な... 結構、あの、大胆な、胸を張って大胆な感じなんですね。
Oh, standing so straight... You're quite bold, sticking your chest out like that.
じゃあ、失礼しますね。
Well then, excuse me.
はい、いつでも。
Yes, anytime.
失礼します。
Here I go.
あー！ スバルが！ あ、ぎゅー！
Ah! Subaru! Oh, big hug!
なんだかすごく、特別な人のような気がする。
I feel like you're someone very special to me.
ルーナも、なんだか、もう離れたくない、一緒にいたい。
I also feel like I don't want to let go. I want to be with you.
スバルも離れたくないような気がする。
I feel like I don't want to let go either.
ルーナ見て、ルーナ見て。
Look at me, Luna. Look at me.
君のことが好きだ。
I love you.
本当？
Really?
スバルと付き合ってください。
Please go out with me.
嬉しい、ありがちゅう。
I'm so happy, thank you.
チュ、チュ、チュ、チュ、チュ。
*Kissing sounds*
嬉しい、ありがとう。これからもよろしく。
I'm so happy, thank you. Let's stay together.
よろしくね。
Let's.
よろしく。
Yeah.
はい、カット、カット、カット！
Okay, cut, cut, cut!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How was that?
いや、清楚な王女様...
Man, what a refined princess...
いや、チョコさ、ちょっと、なんなんだろうね。
Well, Choco, I don't even know what that was.
普段見れないスバルとルーナたんが見れて、これはこれでおもろいのかなって思っちゃった。
Getting to see a side of Subaru and Luna-tan we don't usually see was actually pretty funny.
どういうところが面白かったんですか？
What specifically was funny about it?
スバルが棒読みで、ルーナたんが攻めの姿勢が変わらないんだね。あはは。
Subaru was so robotic, and Luna-tan's aggressive stance never wavered. Hahaha.
勢いがすごいのよ
The momentum was incredible.
あら、そんなつもりはなかったのらけど。あら？
Oh, I didn't mean for it to be like that. Oh?
なんかね、その勢いが強すぎて、なんかちょっと、なんていうんだ、取って食われるみたいな感覚があった
Somehow, that momentum was too strong, and I felt a bit like... how should I say... like I was going to be devoured.
そんなことないのら。
That's not true.
あらあら、なるほどね。
Oh my, I see.
そうなんですよ。えー、じゃあさ...
That's right. Well then...
あ、終わりじゃない、もしかして？
Oh, it's not over yet, maybe?
じゃあちょっと、最後に、ルーナたんが喜びそうなことしてあげるね。
Then, for the finale, let me do something that'll make Luna-tan happy.
なに？なに？
What? What?
じゃあ、スバル、ルーナたん、そこに座って。
Okay, Subaru, Luna-tan, sit there.
もうこのベンチ、トラウマなんですけど。
This bench is giving me trauma already.
とりあえず座ってみなって。
Just try sitting down for now.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
いい、ルーナたん、もうちょっと近寄って。
Okay, Luna-tan, move a bit closer.
おまわりさーん！
Officer!
ルーナたんは、じゃあ目を閉じて。
Luna-tan, now close your eyes.
ほぇー？
Huh?
スバルさんの肩に頭置いて。
Put your head on Subaru-san's shoulder.
ぽてっ。
Thud.
首折れない？
Is her neck okay?
折れないのら。あ、ちょっと王冠が...
It won't break. Oh, the crown is a bit...
突き刺さってる。
It's stabbing me.
そうそう、こうするから。
Right, I'll do this.
あ、いいのら、いいのら。
Oh, this is nice.
そしたらスバルはルーナたんの方を見て。
Now Subaru, look towards Luna-tan.
あー、いいわ、これ！
Oh, this is good!
あー、スバルがルーナたんのおでこにキスしてる！
Ah, Subaru is kissing Luna-tan's forehead!
え？
What?
これは、ぬくもりを感じるショットではないですか！
Isn't this a shot that feels warm!
ぬくもりを感じるのら〜。
Feeling the warmth~.
ちょ、今のチョコ先生の声で耳イカれたんだけど！
Wait, Choco-sensei's voice just blew out my ears!
なに？チョコ先生なんて言った？
What? What did you say, Choco-sensei?
ほぇ、ほぇ。
Hehe.
いや、いいショットが撮れたわ。
I got a great shot.
なるほど、よかったのら。
I see, that's good.
いや、もうチョコ満足！
Man, I'm satisfied!
よかった、よかった。
Good, good.
あれ？チョコ先生が満足して... ルーナが満足するコーナーじゃないのら？
Wait, Choco-sensei is satisfied... wasn't this the "Luna gets satisfied" corner?
でもルーナ、満足した？
But Luna, are you satisfied?
え、もうやばいのら。いろいろやばい。
Eh, it's crazy. Everything's crazy.
最高なのらぜ。
It's the best.
じゃあそろそろね、満足したというところで最後に。
Then, now that you're satisfied, for the finale...
最後、ここからどうするんでしたっけ？
How were we going to end this?
まぁ、一度立ちましょうか。
Well, let's stand up for a moment.
ま、せっかくね、このスバチョコルーナが集まったということなので。
Since the three of us, Suba-Choco-Luna, are together.
チョコ先生、あれ、こっちだよ。
Choco-sensei, oh, over here.
おいで、おいで。
Come here, come here.
揃ったということで。
Now that we're all here.
ここからは３人で歌うのら！
From here, the three of us will sing!
おー！
Yay!
よし、じゃあ一旦、部屋に戻るのら。
Alright, then let's head back to the room.
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
じゃあ、電車で帰ろう。
Then, let's take the train back.
行くよー！出発進行〜！
Here we go! Full steam ahead~!
あまりソワソワしないで
Don't be so restless
あなたはいつでもキョロキョロ
You're always looking around
よそ見をするのはやめてよ
Stop looking away
私が誰より一番
I'm the number one
好きよ 好きよ 好きよ
I love you, I love you, I love you
星たちが輝く夜ふけ
Late at night when the stars shine
夢見るのあなたのすべて
I dream of everything about you
愛してもあなたは知らんぷり
Even if I love you, you play dumb
今ごろは誰かに夢中
Right now you're crazy about someone else
ああ、男の人って
Ah, men...
いくつも愛を持っているのね
Have so many loves, don't they?
ああ、あちこちにばらまいて
Ah, scattering them all over
私を悩ませるわ
You make me worry
あまりソワソワしないで
Don't be so restless
あなたはいつでもキョロキョロ
You're always looking around
よそ見をするのはやめてよ
Stop looking away
私が誰より一番
I'm the number one
ああ、男の人って
Ah, men...
何人好きな人が欲しいの
How many people do you want to love?
ああ、私だけ愛してよ
Ah, love only me
いつでも一人だけを
Always only one person
あんまりソワソワしないで
Don't be so restless
あなたはいつでもキョロキョロ
You're always looking around
よそ見よそ見するのはやめてよ
Stop looking away
私が誰より一番
I'm the number one
私がいつでも一番
I'm always number one
あなたのすべてが好きよ
I love everything about you
好きよ 好きよ 好きよ
I love you, I love you, I love you
一番好きよ
I love you the most
ということで、ラムのラブソング歌ったのら！
And so, we sang Ram's Love Song!
イェーイ！
Yay!
可愛かったー！
It was cute!
可愛かったね、めっちゃ！
It was super cute, wasn't it!
良かったのらー。すごかったのら、二人とも。
That's good. You were both amazing.
なんでこの曲選んだの？
Why did you choose this song?
確かに。
True.
それはもちろん、二人に愛されたかったからなのら〜
That's of course because I wanted to be loved by you two~
あら〜ルーナ様ったらもう、チョコ先生の愛あげるわよ。
Oh my, Luna-sama, I'll give you Choco-sensei's love.
え、本当？チョコ先生の愛もっとちょうだい、もっともっと。
Eh, really? Give me more of Choco-sensei's love, more and more.
はい、ということで！え〜、そろそろ次の曲に行きまーす！
Okay, and with that! Uh, I think it's time to move on to the next song!
え、もう行くの？えー。
Eh, we're going already? Boo.
えー、早い、スバル！
Eh, it's too early, Subaru!
早いとか言わない！段取りがあるんだから、こっちにも！
Don't say it's early! We have a schedule to keep too!
分かったのら。次の曲の…なんだっけ？
I get it. The next song is... what was it?
次の曲の場所に移動するんだよ！
We're moving to the location for the next song!
次の曲の場所に行くために、みんな三日月のほうに乗るのら〜
To go to the location for the next song, everyone get on the crescent moon!
行くのらー！
Let's go!
三日月に乗るのらー。
Getting on the crescent moon.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
こんな感じ？
Like this?
いい感じなのら。
It's good.
じゃあみんな、出航！
Then everyone, setting sail!
イェーイ！出航！
Yay! Setting sail!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our brand new excitement resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
イェーイ！
Yay!
キラメキライダー☆
作詞：辻 純更 作曲：石濱 翔(MONACA)
Kirameki Rider☆
Lyrics: Sumiyo Tsuji Composition: Kakeru Ishihama (MONACA)
覚えてるかな 最初の歌
Do you remember our first song?
懐かしいね
How nostalgic
私の声が震えていた
My voice was trembling
ほんの少し
Just a little bit
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is the today we grasped together
もっともっともっと遠く 加速するハート
Further and further away, our hearts accelerate
一緒に行こう どこまでも
Let's go together, anywhere
あなたに準備はオッケー？
Are you ready?
開け夢の扉を
Open the door to dreams
1, 2, 3! キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3! Kirameki Rider
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our brand new excitement resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's sing together
終わらないメロディー
A melody that never ends
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
届いてたかな 私の声
I wonder if my voice reached you
大好きと
With all my love
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
そのスマイル
That smile
理想の動作に悔しくて
Frustrated by ideal movements
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと 全て抱きしめて
Hold everything tight, tight, tight
一緒に行こう どこまでも
Let's go together, anywhere
あなたに準備はオッケー？
Are you ready?
進め希望の道を
Go forth on the path of hope
1, 2, 3! キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3! Kirameki Rider
好きな気持ちカラフルに奏でたいんだ
I want to play my feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所 最高の仲間と
The best place with the best friends
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm here, it's not an illusion
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is dyed with happiness
重ねてくハーモニー
Layering our harmony
きらめきまとって
Adorned in sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願いはワガママもいいでしょ
Such a wish, even if selfish, is fine, right?
だって楽しすぎて止まらない
Because it's too much fun to stop
輝くステージで もっともっと
On the shining stage, more and more
はい！はい！ずっと！イェーイ！
Hi! Hi! Always! Yay!
ルーナ、おめでとうー！
Happy birthday, Luna!
うれしい たのしい いとしいだけじゃ ことたりない
Being happy, having fun, and feeling loved aren't enough
いまも いまも なやみは あるけど
Even now, I still have worries, but...
ここにいるよ わたし ここにいてよ
I'm right here. Please stay here with me...
きみと おなじ せかいを みつめて
Looking at the same world as you...
いけよ キラメキライダー！
Go, Kirameki Rider!
うまれたての ドキドキを ひびかせよう
Let the fresh excitement resonate...
さいこうの じかん さいこうの なかまと
The best time with the best friends...
ここにいてよ みつけて くれたから
Stay here with me, because you found me...
きみに あいたくて やってきたんだ みんなで うたおう
I came here because I wanted to see you. Let's all sing together...
おわらない メロディー きらめきに のって
An endless melody, riding on the sparkle...
きらめき まとって
Clad in sparkle...
イェーイ！
Yay!
はーい！ということでね、キラメキライダーでした！
Yes! So, that was Kirameki Rider!
ルーナ様大丈夫？おーい！ルーナ様大丈夫？
Are you okay, Luna? Hey! Are you okay, Luna?
大丈夫なのらよ。大丈夫なのらよ。
I'm okay. I'm okay.
今日はルーナが主役だからな！
You're the star today, Luna!
そうなのよ。頑張って、ルーナ様。
That's right. Do your best, Luna.
そうなのらよ。今日はね、この三人でね、おダンスできてすごく嬉しいのらよ！
That's right. I'm so happy the three of us could dance together today!
あーよかった！ね！ちょこも嬉しい！
Ah, that's good! Me too! I'm happy too!
まるでアイドルみたいだよ、スバルたち。
We're just like idols, Subaru and the others.
そうだよ！ね、ルーナたんもアイドルじゃない？
Yeah! Right, Luna? Aren't you an idol too?
いや、アイドルだよ！そうだ、アイドルだった！
Wait, we are idols! Oh right, we were idols!
そうなのらよ！
That's right!
じゃあちょっとね最後だからさ、これで最後の曲なんでしょ？三人でやるのは。
Well, since it's the end... this is our last song together, right? For the three of us.
うん、そう。
Yeah, that's right.
えー！早い！寂しがってくれるなら、え、まだまだ踊る？
Eh! So fast! If you're going to be sad, eh, should we keep dancing?
え、まだまだ？
Eh, more?
え、ちょっと待って、待って待って待って！
Eh, wait a minute, wait, wait, wait!
じゃあ最後だから写真撮るか？写真撮ってみんなで。
Well, since it's the end, should we take a photo? Let's all take a photo.
撮るのら！撮るのら！撮るのら！
Let's take it! Let's take it! Let's take it!
え、ルーナ、ハート作れたのら、ハート。
Eh, Luna made a heart. A heart.
ハートね。ルーナ愛されてるのら。しょうがないわねこれに。
A heart. Luna is loved. Can't be helped.
あ、いい！
Ah, good!
可愛い！ルーナ様そのハートの中に入っちゃっても可愛い！愛されてるのら、ルーナ。
Cute! Luna-sama, you're so cute inside the heart! Luna is loved.
はい、チーズ！
Say cheese!
はい！いいじゃないですか！嬉しいのら！
Yes! Isn't that great! I'm happy!
じゃあ、ルーナ、おめでとうね、本当に。
Well, Luna, congratulations, really.
おめでとう！おめでとうルーナ様！これからも頑張ってね！
Congratulations! Congratulations, Luna-sama! Keep doing your best!
うん、頑張る。この後も頑張るね。ありがとう！
Yeah, I'll do my best. I'll do my best after this too. Thank you!
じゃあちょっと、スバルたちは退散しますから。
Well, Subaru and the others will take our leave now.
またね！頑張ってね！ありがとう！バイバーイ！
See you! Good luck! Thank you! Bye-bye!
はい！スバちょこるーなでした！みんな、お歌どうだった？
Yes! That was Subachoco-Luna! Everyone, how was the singing?
ちょっとコメント見る。三人のお歌とダンスどうだった？
I'll check the comments for a bit. How was the three of us singing and dancing?
可愛い？可愛かった？最高だった？ダンスもね、お歌もね、頑張ったよ！
Cute? Was it cute? Was it the best? I did my best with the dancing and the singing!
本当にスバちょこるーなでね、歌いたいってルーナずっと思っててね。今日、夢が叶いました！
Luna really always wanted to sing as Subachoco-Luna. Today, my dream came true!
スバもちょこ先生も一緒に歌って踊ってくれて本当に楽しかった。
Suba and Choco-sensei sang and danced with me, and it was really fun.
本当に、本当に、本当に二人とも大好き。ありがとうね。
I really, really, really love them both. Thank you.
あとはありのらよね、今ルーナ、スバルに告白されちゃったしね。
And also, you know, Subaru just confessed her love to Luna.
ほら、愛されてるってことでいいのらよねルーナね。えい！今日は最高の日なのら！
See, it means Luna is loved, right? Yay! Today is the best day!
はーい！
Alright!
ということで、ここからは！
And so, from here on!
グッズの告知の時間です！
It's time for the goods announcement!
いきます！デデン！
Here we go! Ta-dah!
おっぱいマウスパッド
Oppai Mousepad
はーい。
Alright.
まずは一つ目はね、かんざきパパ描き下ろしの、
The first item is a new illustration by Kanzaki Papa,
お、おっぱ、おっぱ、おっぱいマウスパッド！
a-an o-oppai, oppai, oppai mousepad!
やばいやばい。
Oh my, oh my.
照れてる表情のルナ、めちゃくちゃ可愛いな、
Luna's blushing face is so incredibly cute,
ルナ可愛い。
Luna is so cute.
ルナのね、この大きいおっぱ、おっぱでね、
With Luna's big oppai, oppai,
みんなのね、このおててをね、休めて欲しいのらよ。
I want you all to rest your hands on them.
おっぱね、おっぱ、おっぱ。
Oppai, oppai, oppai.
そして、二つ目は！
And for the second item!
ルーナイト紋章マグカップ＆コースターセット
LuKnight Emblem Mug Cup & Coaster Set
デデン！
Ta-dah!
見て！
Look!
これな、このマグカップな、ルナのモチーフと、ルーナイトっぽさあるのらよね。
This mug has my motif and a very LuKnight feel to it.
これをね、考えたんで、マグカップになったのら！
I thought about it, and it turned into this mug!
これカップの内側がね、ピンクなの、ピンク。
The inside of the cup is pink, see? Pink.
で、持ち手がハートでな、めっちゃキュートなデザインにしてもらったのらよ。
The handle is shaped like a heart, and I had them make it a super cute design.
やばい可愛い可愛い。
Wow, it's so cute, so cute.
あとね、こちらのマグカップ＆コースターを、この下のね、オリジナルパッケージに入れてお届けします。
Also, this mug and coaster will be delivered in the original package shown below.
なんかさ、昨日ルナさ、モザイク加工して、みんなに見せて、
You know, yesterday I showed a pixelated version of it,
なんかみんなさ、おパンティとかさ、お餅とかさ、言ってたけどさ、
and everyone was saying it looked like panties or mochi,
全然違うのらからね。
but they were totally wrong.
このね、このオリジナルパッケージをモザイクかけた、みんなおパンティとか言ってたけど、
I pixelated this original package, and everyone was saying it looked like panties,
全然違うからね。
but it's completely different.
ルナのら、本当はこんなに可愛いんだからね。
Luna's is actually this cute.
わかった？
Got it?
ということで。
And so...
そして、フルセットでね、こちらを購入すると、
And if you buy the full set,
じゃん！
Tada!
直筆サインとメッセージ入りポストカード、
You'll get a postcard with a handwritten autograph and message,
あとはルナの特典ボイスがついてくるのらよ。
plus Luna's special bonus voice.
こちらは本日22時からBOOTHの方で販売開始をするので、
Sales will start today at 10:00 PM on BOOTH,
ぜひ手に入れてみて欲しいのらーい。
so I'd really love for you to get it.
イェーイ！
Yay!
そして、告知もう二つ目。
And now, for the second announcement.
いきます。デデン！
Here we go. Ta-dah!
歌ってみた『チェリーボンボン』
Cover Song: "Cherry Bonbon"
お、なんと、みんな、10月15日がスバチョコルナ一周年って知ってた？
Oh, did you all know that October 15th is the 1st anniversary of SubaChocoLuna?
ルナもチョコ先生から聞いて知ったんだけど、
I only found out when Choco-sensei told me,
びっくりななのらよ。
so it was a surprise to me too.
ということで、その記念として、10月ね、15日に
And so, to commemorate that, on October 15th,
歌ってみた動画をチョコ先生のチャンネルの方で公開します！
we'll be releasing a cover song video on Choco-sensei's channel!
『チェリーボンボン』というね、可愛いお歌を三人で歌ったので、
The three of us sang a cute song called "Cherry Bonbon",
ぜひね、初めての歌ってみた動画なので、
so please check it out, as it's our first cover song video.
三人のね、スバチョコルナの初めての歌ってみた動画なので、
It's the first cover song video for the three of us in SubaChocoLuna,
ぜひ公開聞きに来て欲しいのらーい。
so I'd really love for you to come and listen when it's released.
楽しみ、楽しみ、楽しみ、楽しみ。
I'm so excited, excited, excited, excited.
そして、まだあと一つ、告知があります。
And there's still one more announcement.
最後の告知は、デデン！
The final announcement is... ta-dah!
お披露目
Reveal
こちら。なんだったて、ルナに新しいマルマル、ん、何これ、にゃん、
This. Apparently, a new "something-something", huh, what's this? "Nyan"?
マルマルが追加された。
Something-something has been added to Luna.
え、みんな、なんだと思う、え、なんだと思うこれ。
What do you all think it is? What do you think this is?
え、え、これ何だ、ルナどうなっちゃってんだこれ。
Eh, what is this? What's happening to Luna?
あー！
Ahhh!
なるほどね、なるほど、うんうん。
I see, I see. Okay, okay.
ま、こちらはね、明日の夜、みんなにね、お披露目します！
Well, I'll be revealing this to everyone tomorrow night!
こちらもね、お楽しみにしていてください！
So please look forward to this as well!
ということで。
And so...
今年はね、素敵なゲストを呼んで、
This year, I was able to invite wonderful guests,
楽しい誕生日をね、過ごすことができました。
and have a really fun birthday celebration.
グッズの発表もね、できて本当にね
Also, being able to announce the goods,
嬉しい気持ちでいっぱい、
I'm filled with so much happiness,
本当にいっぱいいっぱいなのら！
really, so much!
これも全部ね、応援してくれるね
This is all thanks to
みんなのおかげなのら！
everyone who supports me!
最高の誕生日ライブ、ありがとうね
Thank you for the best birthday live.
みんな本当にありがとう
Thank you all so much.
そして最後は
And finally,
とっておきの、ルーナの可愛さを
I'm going to sing a special song
詰め込んだ曲を歌うのら
filled with Luna's cuteness!
聴いてほしいのら！
Please listen!
fancy baby doll
チェックのキャミソールを着て
Wearing a checkered camisole,
今夜ね 遊びに行くわ
tonight, I'm going out to play.
スイートな服はところどころ
My sweet clothes here and there,
君は少し 恥ずかしそうね
you look a bit embarrassed.
ハートのネイルのピンクは 本当はちょっと大ピンチ
The pink of my heart-shaped nails is actually a bit of a crisis.
お行儀出し過ぎのシンデレラ
A Cinderella who's acting too much like a lady,
もっと夢見せて
show me more dreams.
もっとそばに来て
Come closer to me.
Tonight 2人きり Let's party
Tonight, a party for just the two of us.
Happy-fancy baby doll
Love me-fancy baby doll
世界一可愛い子に 生まれたかった
I wanted to be born as the cutest girl in the world.
Happy-fancy baby doll
Love me-fancy baby doll
何万回言われても まだ不安だわ
No matter how many tens of thousands of times I'm told, I'm still anxious.
愛してる
I love you.
カートに溢れてしまうほど
Enough to overflow the shopping cart,
今日はね お買い物の日
today is shopping day.
スイートな帽子と手袋
A sweet hat and gloves,
オシャレすると キラキラするの
when I dress up, I sparkle.
大きなハートがほしい 本当はちょっと弱虫
I want a big heart, the truth is I'm a bit of a coward.
シブめのブーツ脱ぎ捨てて
Throwing off these plain boots,
もっと愛される
I'll be loved even more.
粋か? 女の子
Chic? Girl.
ねぇ 目指したい From my heart
Hey, I want to aim for it, from my heart.
Happy-fancy baby doll
Love me-fancy baby doll
世界一可愛いて 今日も言ってね
Tell me today too that I'm the cutest in the world.
Happy-fancy baby doll
Love me-fancy baby doll
何万回生まれても 君に会いたい
No matter how many tens of thousands of times I'm born, I want to meet you.
本当よ
It's true.
みんな盛り上がってる〜？
Is everyone hyped up~?
今日のルーナ、可愛い？
Is Luna cute today?
え、聞こえないのら〜！
Eh, I can't hear you~!
ありがとう〜！
Thank you~!
もっと盛り上がっていくのらよ〜！
Let's get even more hyped up~!
ハートのネイルのピンクは 本当はもっと大ピンチ
The pink of my heart-shaped nails is actually even more of a crisis.
お行儀出し過ぎのシンデレラ
A Cinderella who's acting too much like a lady,
もっと夢見せて
show me more dreams.
もっとそばに来て
Come closer to me.
Tonight 2人きり Let's party
Tonight, a party for just the two of us.
Happy-fancy baby doll
Love me-fancy baby doll
世界一可愛いって 今日も言ってね
Tell me today too that I'm the cutest in the world.
Happy-fancy baby doll
Love me-fancy baby doll
何万回生まれても 君に会いたい
No matter how many tens of thousands of times I'm born, I want to meet you.
約束よ
Promise me.
今日はルーナのライブ見てくれてありがとうなのら〜！
Thank you for watching Luna's live today~!
これからもずっとよろしくなのら〜！
Please continue to support me forever~!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ルーナイトへ
To Lu-Knights,
毎日嬉しい、楽しい日々が送れるのは
The reason I can spend happy and fun days every day
みんなのお陰なのらよ。
is all thanks to everyone.
本当にいつもありがとう ♡
Thank you so much, as always ♡
ワガママでマイペースなルーナのこと
Please keep watching over Luna,
これからもずっと見守っていてね。
who is selfish and goes at her own pace.
大好き ♡
I love you ♡
2021.10.10
るなよりなのら ♡
From Luna ♡